This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Initial
Raise up your hands　高く [Everybody gonna tell you I can't stop]
Raise up your hands takaku
(Everybody now te wo agero saa)
Tsukame brand new tomorrow
掴め　Brand new tomorrow [You don't stop]
(You don't stop)
風の中で　自分を知る　ずっと最高のDreamだろう
Kaze no naka de jibun wo shiru
Zutto zekkei no dream darou
(Let's go)
Oh[Let's go] Oh[Let's go]
Oh
Oh (Let's go)
Oh raise up you can't stop
Oh, raise up your hands now.
Ikiteru dake de marumouke nara ganbarouze marugoto ittennbari
生きてるだけで何やろうかな
Gamble on　迫る鼓動にテンバリ
同じMission　同じ一生
Onaji mission, onaji isshou
Dondake yume atsuika ga shobu darou
どんだけ夢熱いかが勝負だろ
Escalator nashi no eien
Escalator　無しの永遠
Ashi koshi kitae reruze yeah, yeah
足腰鍛え　Let's begin yeah
Douse noboru kaidan
どうせのぼる階段
心こっちにCustomizeしちゃえばいい
Kokoro kocchi ni customize shichaeba ii
Kezurarete sugiru mainichi
削られて　過ぎる毎日[But you know]
Kezurarete sugiru mainichi (But you know ?)
攻めがいのあるGameと　笑い飛ばして
Semegai no aru game to warai tobashite
Let's see how fast you can do it
Let's see how fast you can do it.
Raise up your hands　ずっと [Everybody gonna tell you I can't stop]
Raise up your hands zutto
(Everybody now te wo agero saa)
Hashire sleepless challenger
走れ　Sleepless challenger [You don't stop]
(You don't stop)
今に生きる　理由を探す
Ima ni ikiru riyuu sagasu
Yume tsukinai quest
夢尽きないQuest
(Let's go)
Oh[Let's go] Oh[Let's go]
Oh
Oh (Let's go)
Oh, raise up your hands now.
Oh raise up you can't stop
涼介
Ryosuke...
何が起こっているんだ
What's going on ?
死神が変だ
The Grim Reaper is acting strange,
showing true hostile intent.
あからさまに殺気を漲らせている
それを受けるあの男も
The other guy is well aware of it,
but he isn't even trying to escape.
それが分かっていながら離脱しょうともしない
This is no ordinary battle.
これはただのバトルじゃない
It looks like I ran into
an extraordinary situation.
俺はとんでもない場面に出くわしてしまったようだ
さすがだな 涼介
Just like you, Ryosuke.
Your earlier hesitation is gone.
先まであった躊躇が消えた
You've got incredible adaptability.
素晴らしい順応力だ
お前は想像以上のドライバーだよ
You're a much better
driver than I expected.
香織 近くに来て 見ているんだろう
Are you nearby, Kaori, watching us ?
I dedicate this battle to you.
このバトルをお前に捧げる
俺は 今夜この場所で死んでも悔いはない
Even if I die here tonight, I won't regret it.
I'm not afraid of anything.
何も怖くないんだ
死神からは逃げられない
No one can escape the Grim Reaper.
あの車 とてつもなく速い
That car is...
...outrageously fast.
本当にやる気なのか 本当に
Is he going to do it ?
For real ?
Full Stop
拓海の話だっと
According to Takumi, that white FC doesn't
sound like Takahashi Ryosuke's car.
やっぱりその白いFC 高橋涼介のじゃないみたいですよ
すると ただの高橋涼介ファンかな
So, it's just a Takahashi Ryosuke fan ?
チラッと擦れ違っただけだって言ってたからな
I only heard it from the guy
who caught a glimpse of it, so...
あ そうそう
Come to think of it,
he said the car had a wing.
そのFC確かウィングが付いてたみたいだって言ってたし
なんだ それじゃ違うよ
Then it's someone else's.
Takahashi Ryosuke's FC has the stock one.
高橋涼介のFCは ノーマルだからな
そうだよな 別人で決まりか
You're right.
It must be someone else, then.
Even though he's retired,
he still has hardcore fans.
引退したっていうのに
未だにコアのファンがいるなんて
さすが赤城の白い彗星 高橋涼介
As expected of Takahashi Ryosuke,
Akagi's White Comet...
クー 羨ましい
I'm so envious.
俺も肖りたいぜ
I wish I could be like him.
いや 無理だろう
That's impossible in terms
of looks, brains, and money.
顔も頭も金も
終わりだ 涼介
You're finished, Ryosuke.
消えろ
Disappear.
No, don't do it !
やっ やめてくれ
狂気の沙汰だ
That's insane !
アテーサE-TSの特性を利用した
Taking advantage of the ATTESA E-TS 4WD system,
he pushed from the side while accelerating.
アクセルオンでのサイドからのプレス
あの重たいボディをまともにくらったら
No one stands a chance
against that heavy body.
一溜まりもない
The Rotary Meister, who used to be known
as the best of the northern Kanto area...
北関東最強とかつて言われたロータリーマイスターが
...will perish in the mountain passes of Hakone.
箱根の峠に散る
Take him, Kaori.
受け取りな 香織
What the hell...?!
何だと
Damn, he climbed up the
slope as if it was a bank.
何と
路肩の斜面をバンク替わりに駆け上がるとは
Impossible.
ありえない
この目で見たものは信じられないぜ
I can't believe what I just saw.
If he forced the car
to stay on the road...
無理にコースに留まろうとあがけば
...it would have hit the curb and
bounced back uncontrollably.
縁石にはねられてとっちらかれ
He aimed straight for the slope,
instead of trying to recover.
立てなおそうとせずに
土手をめがけてまっすぐに駆け上がった
It was a split-second decision. It would
have been too late if he tried to think about it.
とっさの反応なんだ
考えていてはとても間に合わない
He's even more of a natural than
that downhiller, Fujiwara Takumi.
ダウンヒルの藤原拓海に輪をかけるほどのナチュラルっぷりだぜ
ちー 運の強い男だ
You have strong luck,
but how long will it last ?
その強運がどこまで続くかな
Is that all you've got, Senpai ?
こんなもんですか 先輩
I won't run or hide.
俺は逃げも隠れもしない
I won't lose that easily...
簡単には沈みませんよ
...so throw everything you've
got at me, Hojo Rin.
来るなら来い 北条凛
どうしたの 拓海くん
What's wrong, Takumi ?
You spaced out again.
先からぼっとしちゃて
Oh, I'm concerned about that phone call.
あ いや ちょっと先の電話の事が気になって
About an impersonator ?
偽物の話
うん ごめん 電話していいかな
Sorry, but can I make a phone call ?
Sure, no need to worry about that.
いいよ そんな事気にしないで
Thanks. I'll be back in a bit.
悪い ちょっと
Hello ?
もしもし
Oh, Fujiwara, what's up
at this time of night ?
どうした藤原 こんな時間に
Oh, about that...
うん あぁ その件か
Sounds like it's Ryosuke's car.
うん どうやら 涼介の車らしい
No, you don't have to worry.
いや お前は何も心配するな
We don't know where he is, or what he's doing.
どこにいるのかも分からないし
何をしているのかも
I'll hand you over to Keisuke.
うん 今啓介に替わる
Hello, Fujiwara ? Listen.
もしもし 藤原か
よく聴け
You don't have to worry about my brother.
兄貴のことなら心配なんかしなくていい
He's not so weak that he
needs you to worry about him.
兄貴はお前に心配されるほど柔じゃない
Don't worry about this, and just focus
on preparations for the final battle.
気にしないで最終戦の準備に集中しろ
女なんかと遊んでる場合じゃないぜ
This isn't the time to be
goofing around with a girl.
Trust my brother, and don't worry so much.
兄貴を信じろ 心配ない
分かりました
Okay.
Later.
じゃな
Dammit...
クッソ
言えません
I can't say.
It has nothing to do with you.
それは 貴方に関係のない事だわ
But I can't be satisfied until you tell me.
聞かなければ 俺は納得できない
You love someone else, don't you ?
好きな男がいるんだろう
言ってくれ
Tell me the name of the
guy who took you from me.
俺からお前を奪った男の名前を
誰なんだ
Who is he ?
Dad...
パパ
How could you be so selfish ?
なんて勝手の真似をしてくれたんだ
Are you going to destroy everything ?
全てを打ち壊す気か
Everything from my company's
existence to your carefree college life...
私の会社が今あるも
お前がのうのうと学生生活を送っていられるのも
...is owed to Director Hojo.
全て北条院長のおかげだと言う事は知っているだろう
You know that, don't you ?
Change your clothes, Kaori.
急いで着替えなさい 香織
We're going to visit him and apologize.
今から一緒に先方に謝りに行くんだ
If we apologize sincerely,
the Director should forgive us.
誠心誠意謝罪をすれば許してくださるはずだ
I've talked to Rin, and he had the same idea.
凛くんとも話したが そう言ってくれているぞ
イヤです 私は行きません
No, I won't go.
Enough is enough !
How much are you going to trouble me ?
いい加減にしないか
どこまで困らせれば気がすむんだ
私の言う事を聞きなさい
Please listen to me.
お前自身のためでもあるんだ
This is for you, too.
You have no other choice.
それ以外に選択肢などない
I don't want to go, Dad.
行きたくないよ パパ
死んでも 行きたくない
I don't want to go,
even if I have to die.
涼介君
Ryosuke...
さすがはRB26
The RB26 is impressive.
It must be making at least 650 HP.
650馬力は出ている
I'll be out-accelerated
on a long straightaway.
ストレートも長いと ねじ込まれてしまう
すまんな涼介
Sorry, Ryosuke.
This time, there's nowhere to run.
こんどこそ逃げ場はない
情けない 何も出来ないとは
How pathetic.
I can't do anything.
指をくわえて見ているだけか
All I can do is watch ?!
This time there's no bank to climb.
今度は駆け上がる所もない
ガードレールのその先は
Beyond the guard rail is a cliff.
崖だ
立て直した
He recovered ?
The Grim Reaper's fatal
side press didn't work ?
死神渾身のサイドプレスが不発
何が起こった
What just happened ?
Oh, I know.
そうだ
分かったぞ
The speed.
速いんだ
FCの進入スピードが速すぎるんだ
The FC's cornering speed is very fast.
防御は絶対に不可能だと思われていたサイドプレスが
The side press was believed to be
inescapable, but it was completely nullified.
完璧に破られた
見切られた
He dodged my attack by releasing
the side G-force to absorb the impact.
ぶつける瞬間にGを逃がして襲撃を吸収しやがった
なぜだ
Why can't I shoot Ryosuke down ?
涼介を撃ち落せないのは
死神の攻撃に対して
If you follow the basics of slow-in and fast-out,
you'll become a victim of the Grim Reaper.
スローインファーストアウトの基本を守っていては餌食になる
You sacrificed the exit speed
for a high-speed approach.
立ち上がりを犠牲にしてのハイスピードアプローチか
それにしても相手の動きがよく見えている
On top of that, he sees his
opponent's moves very well.
絶対絶命のピンチにも動じないあの精神力
He's so strong-minded that he
doesn't flinch at dire circumstances.
心を閉じる事無く開きながら
Instead of resisting, he remains open
to fear and anger, and lets them go by.
恐怖や怒りを心に留めない
That's the ideal Zero mindset
I've been trying to achieve.
あれこそ俺が目指す理想的なゼロの心だ
俺にはない何かを
He's shown me something I don't have.
あの男は体現している
素晴らしいよ 高橋涼介
You're incredible, Takahashi Ryosuke.
No matter how fast the Grim Reaper's car is,
he's no match for you in a normal race.
いくら速い車でも
まともなバトルなら死神が勝てる相手では無かったな
心のありようがまるで違う
Their mindsets are totally different, and the
Grim Reaper looks noticeably impatient.
あからさまに死神の背中に焦りを見える
That's why, with the GT-R still trailing
behind, the situation is even more dire.
だからこそ
今GTRが後ろにいることの意味が重い
I've never met Hojo Gou of Sidewinder, but
Hojo Rin was three years senior to me in college.
サイドワインダーの北条豪とは まったく面識はないけど
北条凛は大学の三年先輩にあたる人なんだ
俺は北条先輩を助けたい
I want to save Hojo Rin, because
both of us suffer from the same pain.
あの人と俺は 同じ苦しみを抱えている
だからこそ この件は逃げずに受けとめる
That's why I can't run away,
and must face this head on.
それが俺自身のために必要な事でもあるし
I have to do it for my own sake.
The Hojo Rin I knew was sensitive and smart.
俺が知っている北条先輩は
繊細で頭のきれる人だった
本当は何もかも分かっていて
He knew everything, but couldn't
accept it, so he shut himself in.
分かっていながら 納得出来ずに閉じこもっているんだ
キッカケが必要なだけだ
He just needs a chance, and I believe in him.
俺はあの人を信じる
言葉というのは 便利だけど
Words are convenient, but powerless.
無力なものだから
Sometimes you can convey a message
through means other than words.
言葉に頼らないほうが
伝わることもあると思う
難しいですね
What you said is very complex.
涼介さんのいう事は
Besides, I don't understand why it has to be now.
それにしたって
なぜこのタイミングなのかがわかりません
実の兄弟なワケだし
Since they're brothers, Sidewinder and the Grim
Reaper might be collaborating behind the scenes.
サイドワインダーと死神が裏で連携しているとしたら
This could be a trap in order to gain
an advantage in the final Kanagawa battle.
神奈川最終戦を有利に戦うための罠だとも考えられますよ
That's not likely, Matsumoto.
そのセンはないよ 松本
How can you be so sure ?
言い切れるんですか はっきり
理由があるんだ
Hojo Rin picked this date
for a reason, an obvious one.
北条凛が今日という日を指定してきた事には
はっきりと理由が
今日は香織の二回目の命日だ
Today's the second anniversary of Kaori's death.
It's only been two years.
あの日からまだ二年
俺が許せないのは
What I can't stand is that
you've recovered and moved on.
お前がとっくに立ち直って前に進んでいることだ
How can you be so cold-hearted ?
Was it so easy for you to forget ?
薄情な男だな
それほど簡単に忘れてしまえるのか
お前の香織への気持ちは
That's the extent of your feelings for Kaori ?
その程度の物だったのか
違う
No...
傷の深さは
...you shouldn't let the depth of the scar, depth of sadness,
or the intensity of your despair keep you from moving forward.
悲しみの大きさは
絶望して立ち止まってしまうこととは別なんだ
どんなに苦しくても
No matter how strong the pain is,
it's our duty to move forward.
前に進むことは俺たちの義務だ
貴方こそ間違っている
You're wrong for running away from reality.
それはただの現実逃避だ
黙れ 涼介
Shut up, Ryosuke !
You're the one who's running away !
お前こそ逃げている
Both of us are responsible for Kaori's suicide !
香織の自殺は俺たち二人の責任だ
Don't forget that, Ryosuke.
I'll never let you forget that !
忘れるな 涼介
忘れる事は絶対許さん
忘れってなんかいない
I haven't forgotten, nor run away.
逃げてもいない
It has never escaped my mind.
片時も心から消えることはない
だからこそ 進むことが俺の答えだ
That's why I made my
choice to move forward.
You think she wishes for
us to keep fighting like this ?
こんなふうに俺たちがいがみ合うことが
彼女の望みだとでもいうんですか
This will only make her sad !
悲しませるだけだ
分からないのか 北条先輩
Why can't you understand this, Hojo ?
目を覚ませ
Please, snap out of it.
貴方が香織さんの為に俺を追い詰めるというなら
If you intend to drive me into despair,
I'll wake you up for her sake.
俺は彼女の為にも
貴方の目を覚まさせてやる
まずい
Crap.
ブレーキの効きを確かめるようなペダルの踏み方が頻繁に
He's checking the brakes'
effectiveness far too often.
フィーリングがおかしいのか
Is the pedal feeling weird ?
Is there something wrong with the GT-R's brakes ?
GTRのブレーキに何か異変が
元気で今もいてくれれば
I just wished she were alive and well.
それだけでよかった
香織 お前は俺にとって
Kaori, you're the best woman I ever
met, no matter what others say.
最高の女なんだ
誰がなんと言おうと
例え俺の物でなくても
Even if you're not mine, so long
as you're happy, I'd be alright.
お前が幸せなら それでよかったんだ
柔らかな髪 吸い込まれそうな眼差し
Soft hair, a breathtaking gaze...
透き通るように白い肌
...translucent white skin...
細い体 しなやかなライン
...slim body, and gentle curves.
俺にとってお前はアートだった
To me, you're like a work of art.
But you're not here anymore.
けれども お前は もういない
なんと えげつないサイドプレスだ
My god, what a nasty side press !
Instead of thrusting out the nose, he put his
car's body against the other to push it out.
突き飛ばすのではなく
ボディを密着させてグイグイと押しこんでいく
交わす交わせないの次元じゃない
This is not a matter of dodging or not.
ふざけるな死神
You can't be serious, Grim Reaper !
谷に懸かる橋の上だぞ
You're on the bridge over the valley !
ブレーキを踏んでノーズを引っ込ぬいた
He hit the brakes to pull the nose out !
Both cars will lose control at the same time !
二台の姿勢が同時に崩れる
すさまじいな
This is furious.
アンダーステアのGTRが縁石に接触し
The under-steered GT-R hit the curb...
オーバーステアのFCがフルカウンターでラインをクロスさせた
...while the over-steered FC crossed
the line with full counter steering.
まるで果たし合いのような殺伐としたドッグファイトでありながら
No doubt, this is a deadly dogfight.
ハイレベルな技術と技術の応酬が
But I've been witnessing a beautiful exchange
of splendid skills over and over again.
宝石のように煌く瞬間を 何度も魅せつけられるぜ
How I pity you, Grim Reaper.
残念だぜ死神
With such skills, why do you have to turn
your precious car into a lethal weapon ?
それほどのスキルを持ちながら
なぜ大切な車を凶器を変える
落とせないのか これだけ攻めても
I can't get him even if I attack that hard ?
みかけによらず愚直な男だ 涼介
You're foolishly honest,
despite your looks, Ryosuke.
逃げずに受け止めてくれているというわけか
Are you trying to play along with me ?
For what ? For whom ?
何のために
誰のためだ
またか
Again ! Something's wrong.
明らかに何か異変が
The braking distance is getting longer.
制動距離も伸びてきている
It's fatal to have a brake problem
on the downhill of this course.
このコースの下りでブレーキトラブルは致命的だ
その状況でなぜアクセルを踏んでいる
So why is your foot still on
the gas in these circumstances ?!
涼介くんの夢って何
What is your dream, Ryosuke ?
優秀な医者に成ること
To become a good doctor ?
それはいいよ
Sounds good, and I admire it, but...
立派だと思うけど
夢とは言わないよ
...you can hardly call it a dream.
とても現実的な目標だと思う
It's just a practical goal.
男の人には夢があっていいと思う
I think men should be eager to chase dreams.
あたし
Mine ?
Girls are different.
I can live with practical goals.
女の子は違うんだよ
現実的な目標だけで生きていけるから
現実に背を向けて夢に向かって行けるほど強くないから
I'm not strong enough to turn away
from reality to pursue my dream.
だから 夢を負うのは男の人だけの特権だと思う
I think men have the privilege
of being able to chase dreams.
I wish I could keep watching
it with the person I love.
ホントは ずっと好きな人の側にいて
ずっと一緒にそれを見ていられたらいいのに
夢 か
Dream...
What terrible under-steering.
The front tires have no grip.
酷いアンダーだ
フロントタイヤのクリップがもうない
The brakes are even worse than that.
だがそれ以上に
ブレーキはもっと駄目だ
This is unexpected.
誤算だったな
I never thought this game would last this long.
このゲームがこれほど長引くとはまったく考えていなかった
ここの下りはサーキットを走るよりもブレーキに負担がかかる
This downhill puts more stress
on the brakes than the circuit.
このコーナーの出口に 最終の緊急退避所があるんだ
There's one more emergency
escape area beyond the next corner.
If you can't stop, use it, Grim Reaper.
止まれないのならそこに逃げろ 死神
You've done enough !
もう十分だ
いまだ 行け
Now, use it.
You idiot !
バーカーヤロウ
The GT-R's pace is strange.
GTRのペースがおかしい
考えられることは
The possible cause is the brakes.
恐らくブレーキ
まずいな どうする
Damn, what should I do ?
お前には失望したよ 香織
I'm disappointed in you, Kaori.
好きにすればいい
Do whatever you want.
俺もオヤジも今度のことでは不愉快の気分にさせられた
This whole thing has displeased
both my father and me.
後で後悔することに成るだろうな
You'll regret it later.
I hate to say this, but your father's
business will suffer from now on.
嫌な言い方になるが
お前の父親の事業もこの先苦しいだろうね
お前も俺を選ばなかったことを絶対に後悔する時が来る
Someday, you'll regret
that you didn't choose me.
深い意味は無かった
It didn't have any deep meaning.
悔し紛れに口走った ただの戯言だ
I couldn't help saying such a foolish
thing because I was so frustrated.
香織 お前を追い詰めたのは俺なのか
Kaori, was it me who
drove you into a corner ?
あれだけインをカットしてもまだラインが膨らむ
It slid outward that much even
though it had an inside line.
制動力がもうほとんどないのか
It may have lost most
of its braking potential.
こうなれば死神に残されている手段は
All that's left is for the Grim
Reaper to launch a suicide attack.
自爆とも言える体当たりしかあるまい
逃げろ 高橋涼介
Run, Takahashi Ryosuke. Shake him off.
そいつを振りきっていけ
残念だが今の死神が正気じゃない
I'm afraid the Grim Reaper has lost his mind.
付き合うことはない
You don't have to continue playing his
game. Get out of his attack range.
射程距離の外へ逃げってくれ
Why did you release the accelerator
way before the braking point ?!
なぜブレーキングポイントの遥か手前でアクセルを抜くんだ
だぜここで減速する
Why did you slow down here ?!
What the...?!
何を
What're you doing, Ryosuke ?!
何をしている涼介
止められるわけがない
You can't stop the heavy body of the R32.
この重いR32の車体を
こっちのブレーキはもう完全に抜けとるんだ
My brakes are completely gone.
二台分の車重を受けとめるのは
Your FC's brakes can't
take the weight of two cars !
そのFCのブレーキでは無理だ
さよなら 涼介君
Goodbye, Ryosuke.
何言ってるの
What are you talking about ?
Kaori, where are you now ?
香織さん 今どこ
今までありがとう
Thank you for everything.
Although it was brief, I had fun.
短い間だけど 楽しかったよ
どこにいるか言ってよ
Tell me where you are.
I'll be right there.
すぐにそっちにいくから
君に会えてよかった
I'm glad I met you, Ryosuke.
涼介君
さよなら
Goodbye.
二台の軸がズレていて
It's so hard to maintain control
because the two cars are misaligned.
バランスが取りにくい
取り返しのつかないミスだったな
It's an unrecoverable mistake.
制動力をマックスに立ち上げられない
I can't get the maximum braking ability.
駄目だ
It's no good, we aren't slowing down.
スピードが落ちってない
止められない
I can't stop !
Fujiwara Takumi:
Takahashi Ryosuke:
Hojo Rin:
Kaori:
Ikeda Ryuji:
Matsumoto:
Miki Shinichiro
Koyasu Takehito
Nakamura Yuichi
Endo Aya
Nakai Kazuya
Nishi Rintaro
Yuugure ni kawaranai keshiki
日の暮れに　変わらない景色
Takahashi Keisuke:
Uehara Mika:
Iketani Koichiro:
Kenji:
Takeuchi Itsuki:
Fumihiro:
Kaori's Father:
Seki Tomokazu
Hayami Saori
Yao Kazuki
Takagi Wataru
Iwata Mitsuo
Hosoi Hajime
Omoro Masayuki
Furikaeru tadottekita michi
振り返る　辿ってきた道
Setsunasa mo, yorokobi mo, kienai itami mo
切なさも　喜びも　消えない痛みも
Kazoetetara kiri ga nai ne to hitori aruku
数えてたら限がないねと独り歩く
A
Central Anime
Production
Translation:
Hiro-kun
Timing:
Todd Perkins
Editing:
Lillian-Hime
Barbara
Todd Perkins
Brain
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Namke
Kazoekirenai hodo no zanzo
数え切れないほどの残像　ギャンブル生き抜いてきた残党
Gambaru ikinuite kita zattou
Toki ni tatakai toki ni wakari ai
時に戦い　時に解りあい　きれい事ばかりじゃなかった真実
Kireigoto bakari ja nakatta shinjitsu
Shotta mama arata na ippo
背負ったまま新たな一歩
Akane gumo ga machi wo someru
あかね雲が街を染める　この行く先をそっと問いかけて見る
Kono yuku saki wo sotto toitakete miru
空はなにもいわず　だけど私にこの道を照らしている
Sora wa nani mo iwazu
Dakedo watashi ni kono michi wo terashiteiru
透き通る景色を感じて
Sukitooru keshiki wo kanjite
Senritsu wo yuuhi ga kanadete
旋律を夕陽が奏で
Sukitooru keshiki wo kanjite
透き通る景色を感じて
Senritsu wo yuuhi ga kanadete
旋律を夕陽が奏で